[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, I'm home.
(Howard:)Of course.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Senior fitness was canceled.
(Howard's Mother:)It turns out you can forget
how to ride a bike.
(Howard's Mother:)I'm fine, but, oy,
did Sam Harpootian eat gravel.
(Howard:)That's great, Ma.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: What's great
about an 80-year-old Armenian man...
(Howard's Mother:)...with half his chin scraped off?
(Bernadette:)-I guess I should go.
-No, don't move.
(Howard:)Hey, Ma,
can I have lamb stew for dinner?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Lamb stew?
I'd have to go to the supermarket.
(Howard:)Please? I got a real hankering.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Oh, I can't say no
to my little tushy-face.
(Howard's Mother:)-I'll be back soon.
-Thanks, Ma.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Do you want the
regular peas or the Le Sueur?
Always Le Sueur peas
with lamb stew.